I may not be a professional gumshoe, but I still do enjoy a good ol' detective LARP.
And I do say not to toot my own horn. I'm not bad at it. Am I the best detective in the world?
Yeah. Probably.
A lot of people call me the bearded L from Death Note.
I once cracked the case on the whereabouts of D.B. Cooper.
Don't need to get into the weeds of that again, but long story short, official narrative was wrong.
He did survive the jump from the plane, only to perish at Dashcon Furry Convention 2014 in the ball pit.
Anyway though, I wanted to put these skills to the test here because I just saw something pretty interesting here.
A case that on the surface seems simple, straightforward, not overly unusual.
It was a man selling his scooter to another man and ended up with the scooter being driven away, stolen out from underneath him.
A song and dance you've heard a million times, especially with things like Facebook Marketplace where shit's happening every five minutes.
And to the untrained eye, it seemed like just another one of those instances.
But...
Rabbit hole goes deeper than you might think. Let's start here at the beginning.
It's smoothing you man. Yeah, yeah, this is you there.
Can you give me a guide on like how to...
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, it's really good. Especially if the it's it's it's have a good battery.
A few moments later.
Bruh.
Oh my god!
Where you going?
The spamming of TikTok and YouTube short sound effects there, the meme stock sound effect package.
Kind of annoying, but this is what happened.
So he brings the scooter here for this deal.
He asks, can I ride it? You know, take it for a bit of a test drive, a little spin there.
And so he pulls out a little bit, does a little peer away and then just peels out going through the gas station.
And the seller then starts giving chase, jogging after him like, where are you going?
Hey!
Man!
Boy!
Hey!
Help!
Help me!
My scooter was stolen!
He tries to alert others in the area that his scooter has been stolen asking for help, but no one steps in to like clothesline him or anything like that.
It's just a low speed pursuit here. I don't even think that's top speed on the scooter.
I think this guy was just doing it to like taunt him.
Like just stay just barely out of range because it sounds like this guy is running in like sandals or flip-flops or something.
So he's not able to really like fucking zip at him there, like really start zooming or anything.
So he's just doing the best he can to keep up as he's getting further and further away.
And I know what you're thinking here where like, oh maybe this is a fake video. Maybe this is like a rage bait type of thing.
Maybe it's all like phony baloney for the sake of being a viral video.
And I thought the same at first too because it does feel like a little wacky because when you're doing a deal like this, I think it's kind of commonplace that when someone asks to test it, you will say,
all right, you're going to need to like give me like some of the money up front or give me something to like hold on to.
So that way there's not really like mitigates the risk of them just like running away because now they'll be out money or like their phone or something like that.
But he didn't do that here. He just instantly lets them hop on.
So it sounds like, well, maybe it's fake. Maybe that's maybe that's what the big mystery is here, you know.
But it's not fake, actually.
This is a very real thing that the authorities are investigating.
He has filed a police report and they are like looking into trying to find the thief and get the scooter back.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, help me. My scooter.
My scooter was stolen.
I feel really bad for the guy like trying to chase him down here, but to no avail, because the scooter is going faster than he can run.
Like those guys they're so väldigt, very обс nurses let's make a trailer.
Dad! My scooter was stolen!
I feel really bad for the guy, like, trying to chase him down here, but to no avail, because the scooter is...
going faster than he can run.
Like, those scooters can get up to, like, 30 sometimes. I don't think he's going 30 there by any means.
He's keeping it pretty slow there. There's a ton of people around, so I'm assuming he doesn't want to, like, run into them and, like,
you know, fucking...
fly off there, like, it's GTA 4 and you blast through the windshield or anything.
So he's been keeping it kind of slow, but just fast enough to be
out of range for this guy who's been chasing him now for going on almost two minutes.
And he's trying, like, calling out, like, hey, he stole my scooter, help, that kind of thing, and it's just not working.
That fucking sucks. That must be an absolutely terrible feeling.
Help! Help!
My scooter was stolen!
Help! My scooter was stolen!
Please help me!
Help! My scooter!
Help!
Unfortunately, we cannot complete your call.
Help! My scooter was stolen!
Entering your call again.
Help!
Unfortunately...
So he makes off with the scooter. There was no one that was, like, stepping in to stop him, though that would have been pretty difficult to do.
It's not like they'd just be able to fucking throw out a spike strip or something on the scooter. So
he was unable to, like, get it back there.
So instead went to the authorities who are now looking into it to try and find,
uh, the thief and get the scooter. So it was real. This is a real video and this is blown up. Now where it gets
very interesting is that it turns out this same guy had this exact same thing happen just two weeks ago
in very similar circumstances.
Yep.
So how long did you, uh, own this? This one is just a couple of months ago.
Yep. So like how much kilometers? Um, we can check it maybe like around
400?
Oh, yeah, or 500. It's just once just for a couple of times. Okay.
Um, this is the charger. Now this happened at the end of June. So it predates the scooter robbery
we just watched the the scooter heist.
So he is now selling this is a different scooter to someone else once again through like an online
marketplace here.
And so now he is bringing the scooter there for the deal. It goes 30. Yep.
Okay. So, um, can I just make sure it goes 30? Yep. Sure. Okay. It's like, uh, can I hold something? All right. Okay.
Let's try it. Maybe from there going here it will go 30.
Okay.
The audio cuts out here, but the dude just goes full throttle here and just has that bitch fucking sail off into the sunset
going straight to Narnia.
It's extremely unlucky that this has happened to him twice and this was the first recorded instance of it.
And in this interaction, he actually did ask to hold something of the buyer.
To try and prevent the scooter from being stolen to try and reduce the risk of that happening because now he's got the guy's phone
surely he wouldn't just
run off with the scooter and leave this.
But
he did.
And what was interesting is in the video
when he asks, you know, can I just double check to make sure it can go 30?
Can I make sure that these nuts got juice in them? Can it, you know, really get on there grab the bull by the horns?
Let me take her out here. He's like, okay, sure.
And as he like is saying that the guy's already reaching into his pocket getting his phone
and then the the guy selling it says let me just hold something of yours and then gets the phone.
So like I'm assuming that the the thief here has probably done this a time or two.
Or I guess there's also a chance that this is like scripted. Like it is fake.
But it's I feel still unlikely because in this case too from two weeks ago
he did file another police report as well. And like in his whole post here
he goes into information on the guy here because he got a lot of the guy's personal information and everything.
And I also don't see what the purpose would be because this isn't like an influencer or content creator looking for viral stories or anything.
Like he has these two videos on his Facebook page and that's like all I can find.
So like I guess if it is
like phony baloney, maybe the goal is to like
make people more aware of the dangers of selling on online marketplaces.
But again, that's another big stretch. So anyway, the phone that he got was locked down. So it was
probably a stolen phone.
So he the phone ended up being like a fucking brick.
It's just so odd because it's happened twice to him now in two different instances.
Like I guess maybe another thing is that he's doing this on purpose with the scooters and stuff to try and like
catch thieves as like maybe like some vigilante type justice.
Maybe that?
But again, I don't know that that also still feels like a fucking stretch. In this one though,
it's very odd because this is two weeks two weeks ago and he does ask to hold the guy's phone, which
is smart. So that way there's less chance that he's just gonna fucking
you know, go hog wild with the scooter and run away with it. And then two weeks later
during another sale, he doesn't ask to hold anything of the buyers.
So then he just gets on their raw dog and runs away with it.
I guess
maybe another option would be to like bring the scooter there with like zero percent charge or like one percent charge so they can do like
one like one big rip like hit a wheelie and then
peters out so that way they can't like get away with it per se. Anyway, though
in the first rodeo, he did take a step to try and you know,
mitigate the risk of it being stolen. Second time around he just decided not to, throwing caution to the wind even though
he was already the victim of theft. He already had a previous scooter stolen.
So why? It's just a little confusing to me is all.
So here's what I think putting on my detective top hat and smoking my pipe.
I don't think these are fake. I think these are very real. It'd be
very fucking peculiar for someone to agree to do this and then have police reports filed on them as criminals. Like
I highly doubt anyone would be willing to do that,
especially when there doesn't even seem to be like a motivator for like
internet attention or clout or anything. It doesn't seem like he's trying to gain anything out of this aside from getting his
scooters back and getting justice. So I don't think it's fake. I don't think either of these two cases are fake. I also
don't think that this is him trying to like,
you know, use this as bait to catch thieves. Like I don't think this is some kind of like bait car
scenario or anything like that because if that was the plan, if that was the goal,
I imagine he probably would have done something to ensure they don't actually get away with the merchandise, the expensive items here.
Like there have been YouTubers that have done that kind of thing before where they have like a bicycle and like fucking self-destructs or something
so they don't actually
steal
the the item. Here they do just make off with his expensive shit here and he's just left with his dick in his hand.
So that sucks. Like I I don't think that this was all like a plan from him. Like some kind of calculated bait car,
catch thieves type thing. I don't think it was fake or you know, made for views or virality.
What I think, the truth of it is, I think this guy is just extraordinarily unlucky.
I think he is doing business in a bad part of town here and
now twice in the course of two and a half weeks, he's had his
scooter stolen. I think the first time around when the guy gave him his phone and still stole the scooter,
he probably just thought, okay, well this this doesn't actually help anything at all.
So maybe next time I won't even bother. Which I think is why he didn't do it with the other buyer there that recently
stole it because he had already experienced that holding an item
didn't actually protect him. So he just didn't even bother.
And then his scooter got stolen again, which fucking sucks. I feel extremely bad for this guy here.
I would say probably stop trying to sell in this part of town would be what I'd recommend or
instead of like holding an item, just outright say,
no, you can't take it for a ride under any circumstances unless you pay up front.
Then you can take it for a ride and if you're not satisfied maybe a refund whatever.
But yeah, after diving into the the meatballs here, I think this is all very legitimate.
I think this is someone that was actually trying to sell these scooters
and had them stolen both times, unfortunately.
Hopefully he can get them back. Hopefully the thieves get found and brought to justice.
I also read something that I haven't been able to confirm through other sources
that the sale of these scooters was actually like very important for this guy and his family.
Apparently for like a upcoming bill, like a hospital bill, I saw that reported.
I don't know if that's been confirmed anywhere because I can't see anything else that talks about that.
But if that is the case, then that's fucking heartbreaking.
Either way, I do feel bad for him because I do believe this is just a very legitimate case of a guy
being the victim of two thieves stealing his scooters here and leaving him out a bunch of money on it.
Anyway, that's really about it. See ya.