What the freak did you just freaking say about me you little sh**?
Oh how did you know I graduated top of my class in the Navy SEALS and I have been involved in numerous raids on Al Qaeda and I have over 300 confirmed kills.
I'm trained in guerrilla warfare and I am the top sniper in the entire US armed forces.
You are nothing to me but just another target.
I will wipe you the f**k out with precision the last time which I've never been seen before on this earth.
Mark my f**king words.
You think you can get away with saying that sh** to me over the internet?
Those comments?
Think again f**ker.
As we speak my secret network of spies is being contacted all over the USA and your IP is being traced right now.
So you better prepare for that storm maggot.
The storm that wipes out the pathetic thing that you call your life.
You're f**king dead kid.
I can be anywhere anytime and I can kill you in over 700 ways and that's just with my bare hands.
Not only am I extensively trained in unarmed combat but I have access to the entire arsenal of the United States Marine Corps and I will use it to its full extent to wipe your miserable ass off the face of this continent you little sh**.
If only you could have known what kind of holy retribution that little clever comment, that little clever hate comment was about to bring upon you.
Which is wrong.
Maybe you would have held your f**king tongue.
But you couldn't and you didn't and now you're paying the price you god damn idiot.
My opinion is always right and I will sh** fury all over you and you will drown over it.
You're f**king dead kiddo.