Hey, everybody, how's it going?
Hope you have an lovely day.
Today, I want to respond to a legal notice that I got asking me
to remove content from my website.
If you've been watching my videos for any length of time,
you imagine you don't need a spoiler to understand
how this is going to go.
What I wanted to do before I do that is explain
how I do business and why I do business in the way
that I do when it comes to my marketing
and how I present myself on my company website,
what my strategy is.
I want to give you an example from a long time ago.
If you are trying to fix your own laptop,
let's say that you broke the screen.
On average, your normal user that's not a technician
is not going to open the device, take the screen out,
get the part number from it, and then Google the part number
to buy it.
What they're going to do is they're going to look
at the bottom of the device.
They're going to read where it says model, A1181.
They're thinking of Google, A1181 MacBook screen,
and they're usually going to buy what shows up,
and then they're going to take it apart once they get the device.
Because most people, they don't want to do an extra tour
of taking the device apart twice.
And especially if the screen is half working,
you don't want to mess with it while it's half working.
Now, the reason that this is something
that could present a problem is that the model number
of the part, if you search for that,
is actually going to get you a lower price
than if you searched by the model number with a laptop.
So let's say that you were to search for A1181 MacBook screen.
You may find websites selling it for $1500 to $200.
But if you search for the actual part number of the screen,
which you have to take the entire device apart to see,
if you search for LP133WX1, you may find the part
as cheap as $50 to $70.
And the reason that many websites did this back in the day
is because they realized that they want to be able to charge
more money to people who'd know necessarily no better,
but they also don't want to lose business
from technicians buying the part.
So if you go to their website and you search
for A1181 MacBook screen, it'll be listed for $150.
But if you search for LP133WX1,
the exact same device that will be shipped to you
will cost you $50.
My website is very ugly back then, as you can see.
I think I made this in eBay's HTML editor for website,
I mean, for product postings, it was horrible.
But I knew that I was not going to be able to compete based
on having the fanciest website.
I had $200 in my pocket.
I wasn't going to be able to pay a fancy developer.
So what I decided to do is I am just going to operate
in a very honest and transparent way.
There's this idea in life that you need to climb
and compete with other people climbing their hierarchies.
And that's not what I do.
I always forget I'm just going to make my own.
And in my industry, I realized that there was a severe lack
of honesty and transparency.
Those websites were technically not doing something
that was illegal.
They didn't do something that's wrong, per se,
but you wouldn't feel good if you were on the other end
to that.
And I realized when I made my website that there's a very good
chance that if somebody sees that they could buy this part
of $50, they may be less likely to use me
than they would be if they thought the part was $150.
And I was just charging $10 in labor.
And I didn't care.
If that meant that somebody did the work by themselves,
great, more power to them.
I never wanted people to feel like they were doing business
with me because they had to or because they were coerced
into it.
I wanted them to be as informed as possible.
I wanted them to understand our industry.
And then once they have a full understanding
of our industry, do business with me
because they want to, because they feel like I am the best option
for them at that time.
And I've always carried this forward
in how I do business with all the border pair videos I did
with having a detailed weeky that goes over
how to do all the repairs that I do even if you don't want
to watch my videos.
And I've carried that forward with data recovery.
I have a data recovery business right now.
And data recovery is an industry that I believe is highly
treacherous.
Do you agree, Blackberry?
Good girl.
There are a number of examples I could give you.
I'm just going to give you a few real quick ones over here.
There's a company called Drive Savers.
Almost every single person in this industry has had that moment
where you have a customer go to you.
And they give you something like a phone that has a bad screen
and you get told that Drive Savers wanted $2800
to do data recovery.
Or it has a bad charge port.
And I took it to Drive Savers.
They said it was going to be $3,000.
I asked for it back.
And there's a lens in the charge port or something like that.
It's really crappy because technically
they're not actually doing something illegal.
They are offering you a data recovery service for a price.
They tell you the price upfront, you pay the price.
And they give you your data, you technically got what you paid for.
There's no specific crime to point to there.
However, if your elderly grandmother paid $2800
solely because she lacked the technical knowledge
and know how to understand that the only problem
with her phone was a bad screen, you'd probably be really angry.
And I'm going to take a wild guess that when the only problem
with the phone is a bad screen, they're
not telling their customer $2800 screen repair.
And the reason that this stuff happens
is because this is old memo from almost 30 years ago
where Apple is referring a lot of the data recovery customers
to drive savers if they want to keep their warranty.
That gave them some legitimacy.
And they've built on that in a way that I find to be really shitty.
My website also debunks other concepts
such as the requirement for a $2 million clean room
in order to do data recovery.
You'll often see websites where people wear
in these fancy spacesuits are there
while you need a clean room for data recovery.
They'll tell you about their $2 million clean room.
And I made an entire page on my website debunking this.
For less than the cost of a big screen television,
you too can have a laminar flow bench, which allows you
to do the exact same work to the exact same standard
that they would do in a clean room.
I spent more money on this damn particle counter
that I did on my entire laminar flow bench set up
just to make sure that I had a calibrated instrument
that could prove that that $4,000 laminar flow bench
allows you to get a particle count of zero
at stuff that you can't even see with a microscope
and do data recovery just fine.
The reason I'm doing this is because I don't want people
to believe that when they get these outlandish
psychotic quotes for data recovery,
that's the $2 million clean room that you're paying for.
And that's why it's so much money.
The reality is that what you're paying for in many instances
is marketing.
A lot of the companies that are telling you this
are paying for ads and these ads can be upwards
of $150 per click and they have to make that back somehow.
There are also other practices in the industry
that I go over on a regular basis on my website,
such as the fake data recovery locations.
You'll have companies that have a bunch of different
locations all across the country.
And when you show up, there's nobody there.
There's nobody there that actually does data recovery.
And sometimes the people that are there
are not even employees at the company.
One of the things that you'll note if you look
for data recovery in my area is that
there's one or two companies that actually do it.
But then there's a bunch of other companies
where when you show up, you're not going to see
a PC 3000 or a data recovery lab.
A lot of these locations don't actually have tools
for data recovery and the company that my company,
which does have all the tools on site for data recovery
and thousands more have used in those
are essentially at the bottom.
So I'll have people show up to my store
on a regular basis saying, hey, you're the third or fourth place
I went to, the first two or three places I went to
didn't even have a technician on site.
And the person that was there said
that they didn't even work there.
And I'll go, what, what are you talking about?
And I'll say, yeah, look at all these other places
that outrank you on Google.
They don't even have somebody working there
who does data recovery.
So I decided to start looking into this.
And when I looked into it, I made a page on my website,
fake data recovery locations that goes over
and documents this practice in detail.
Most people when they show up to a business
that they looked up on Google Maps,
they want somebody to be that knows what they're doing.
So if you needed some screws, some nails,
and a screwdriver, you might go on Google Maps
and go hardware store.
And then when you go to the hardware store,
you're expecting to find somebody that actually knows
about hardware.
If you went to the hardware store that you found on Google Maps
and they had no screwdrivers, no nails,
and you asked them, what's the difference between a Phillips
and a flathead and they told you,
I don't know and I don't even work here,
you might feel like you got swindled.
If you were hungry and you search for restaurants on Google
and you see Mike's burger joint
and you show up to Mike's burger joint.
And the person who's in the front doesn't make burgers,
they don't have a grill, they don't have any meat,
and they tell you they've never made a burger,
like what are we even doing here?
This is a common annoyance that my customers will tell me
they have when they go to businesses in the area.
And I decided to make a page on my website
that goes over all of this.
My website has lots of information on these practices
and the companies that engage in these practices
so that you understand how our industry works.
But it's not all just saying that these companies
have these problems.
We also talk about competitors in a positive light,
some of which actually charge less money than we do.
I have a page on my site called
Honest Data Recovery Companies
where I talk about other competitors
that I believe do business in an honest way.
Ipad rehab, desert data recovery,
$300 data recovery, and a bunch more
if you visit datarecoveryprofessionals.org.
If you go to datarecoveryprofessionals.org,
you'll find a group of like-minded people
that don't take part in these deceptive practices.
And I'm very happy to promote that on my own website,
even though they're all direct competitors,
because I believe that we're better off
if we have a more honest industry.
I know that there's no way in hell
that my half a dozen employee team
can do data recovery for the entire country.
And I'm happy to promote people
that I think are doing honest work.
And I have no problem if that means
that they get a job that maybe would have went to me.
Now, this brings us to the cease and desist
that I got from the law office of Zachary,
a Western Hauffer, and the response
that I'm gonna be giving, which I imagine you can predict here.
Falsimus leading commercial statements concerning
we recover data.
Mr. Rossman, this office represents werecoverdata.com,
WRD, it has come to our attention
that you and Rossman repair group
have published a lengthy webpage titled
is we recover data safe.
That contains false misleading
and commercially disparaging statements
concerning WRD and its services.
The webpage is expressly attributed to you
as the founder and chief technician
of Rossman repair group bank.
It is not presented as a neutral news report
or an abstract discussion of industry practices.
Instead, it repeatedly attacks WRD's integrity,
business practices, technical capabilities, pricing,
customer relationships, and fitness to provide data
recovery services while directly comparing WRD
with your competing data recovery business.
It concludes by soliciting readers to retain
Rossman repair group for the same services.
WRD recognizes that competitors may engage
in truthful, comparative advertising,
and may express honestly held opinions concerning
matters of legitimate public interest.
WRD does not seek to suppress protected opinion,
fair criticism, or the accurate
read publication of verified facts.
Your webpage, however, goes materially farther.
It presents serious accusations of misconduct
as established facts, republishes support unsupported
accusations from third parties as reported evidence,
and uses those accusations to divert
prospective customers towards your competing business.
Among other things, your website states
or communicates that.
WRD maintains fake or misleading business locations
and that the 22 locations you reported investigated
are virtual offices that fail applicable criteria.
WRD has engaged in a consistent pattern
of pricing escalation, non-refundable charges,
punitive cancellation, terms of withholding customers'
devices, spending payment.
WRD's published technical materials contain
fabricated claims, dangerous advice,
and engineering impossibilities and false assurances.
WRD advertises a fabricated success rate.
WRD's technical capabilities, equipment, credentials,
facilities, and customer service practices
are materially inferior to those of Ross
from the Pair of the Bank, and WRD deliberately damages
customer property when customers decline WRD quotes
or seek competing services.
The final category is particularly serious.
Your webpage, republishes a statement attributed
to the Reddit user, Zorb 750, accusing WRD
of being strongly suspected of sabotaging hard drives
when customers decline their quote.
It also republished a statement attributed
to Reddit user, Data Recovery NJ, claiming,
I have had a few cases with re-recovery data
where they quoted the customer 4,000 plus
when the customer asked for it back
to copy the data to their server and DGOS to drive.
WRD understands that data recovery NJ is associated
with a competing data recovery business.
Your decision will republish that accusation
to your company's website gives it a broader audience
and places the authority, reputation,
and commercial interests of Ross from the Pair of the
behind it.
The accusation is false.
WRD does not sabotage DGOS, destroy or deliberately
damage customers' drive because the customer declines quote,
request the return of the device or elects to obtain
services elsewhere.
WRD does not copy customer data and then
intentionally runs the original device
unrecoverable as retaliation for a customer's decision
not to proceed with the quoted service.
These accusations directly attack WRD's honesty, integrity,
and fitness to perform data recovery work.
Your webpage also appears as a sign of capture consumers
actively searching for information concerning WRD
and redirect them towards Ross from the Pair of the Bank.
The page repeatedly contrasts alleged deficiencies
in WRD's services with the reported advantages
of your competing business, including
your pricing, equipment, evaluation policy, facilities,
consumer reviews, and no data, no fee policy.
The commercial purpose of the publication
is apparent from its structure, content and concluding
solicitation.
Your concept appears to give rise to multiple cases of action,
including claims for defamation and defamation per se,
business disparagement, entree, libel, torches,
interference with prospective business relationships,
unfair competition, and false remiss leading
representations of fact and commercial advertising
or promotion and violation of WRD is continuing to review
the web page and source of sight within it.
Nothing in this letter should be understood as limiting WRD's
objections to the examples identified above WRD expressly
reserve the right to identify additional false misleading
unsupported and materiously and concluding
the statements concerning WRD.
Accordingly, WRD demands that you and Ross from the Pair
group immediately remove publication, the website
entitled is we recover data safe in its present form.
Two, immediately sees publishing, republishing,
distributing or promoting any false or misleading
statement that WRD sabotaging negosses, destroys,
damages deliberately renders customers' devices
and recoverable, immediately sees publishing,
republishing false or misleading factual statements
concerning WRD services, pricing practices, locations,
facilities, personnel, technical capabilities,
credentials, customer relationships and business practices,
remove any material identical or substantially similar
publication concerning WRD from any other website.
Social media account, advertising platform,
provide a written identification of each website, blah, blah, blah,
if you contend any accusation of sabotage of this.
Yeah, let's see, I'm sorry, I'm just,
I'm laughing because I'm impatient to get to the fun part
of the video.
WRD is preserved evidence related to your publication,
including copies of the web page, publication dates,
source links, screenshots, archive materials,
and related records.
You and Ross from the Pair group,
hereby placed a notice that WRD anticipates litigation,
considering the vat is adjusted this letter.
Accordingly, you are under a legal obligation
to preserve all potentially relevant evidence
in your possession, custody or control.
This includes, without limitation, all drafts,
edits, revision history, source materials, screenshots,
archive pages, analytics records, search engine optimization
records, keyword search materials, advertising records,
website traffic records, conversion data,
customer intake records, referral records, emails,
text messages, internal communications,
social media communications, Reddit posts,
the rec messages, account records,
made data, browser data, customer communications,
business records, financial records,
and electronically stored information relating
any way to WRD.
The web page entitled, is we recover data safe,
any other statement concerning WRD.
The statement is attributed to Zorb 750 and Data Recovery NJ.
The NN communications with those users
or with the persons responsible for those accounts,
and any effort to direct actual or prospective customers
away from WRD or towards Ross from the Pair group
or any competing service.
You are further directed not to delete, modify, destroy,
override, conceal, or permit the loss of any such materials
whether stored locally in cloud accounts,
a mobile device's business systems,
or through third party platforms.
This preservation obligation applies equally
to Ross from the Pair group bank
and to each of his officers, employees, agents,
contractors, representatives.
Failure to preserve it relevant evidence
after notice of anticipated litigation
may constitute a poilation of evidence
and may subject you in Ross from the Pair group
into court and post sanctions.
Adverse, evidentiary, interferences,
monetary penalties or other relief.
Nothing in this letter constitutes a complete reduction
of WRD's factual, illegal positions,
all of which are expressly reserved.
We request written confirmation by no later than July 8th
that you and Ross from the Pair group
will comply with the four going demands.
If you've ever complied WRD's prepared
to pursue litigation and all available legal remedies
without further notice to you,
govern yourself accordingly.
Sincerely, Zachary A. Weston Hauffer.
Council for rewecoverdated.com.
I keep having to edit this
because I keep laughing too much throughout it.
I apologize for that.
I like doing these more in one take,
but I can't do it on this one.
So what was one of the items that they were complaining about?
WRD advertises a fabricated success rate
is what they attribute to me.
Let's see what their page says and what my page says.
So on my page, it says the website
advertises a 96% success rate in page title tags
where their own FAQ stays, they do not publish success rates.
Let's see if they actually removed this
or edited this from the website
before sending a season to assist.
At this point, they have had literally two weeks
to cover their tracks on this
and let's see what they did.
So if I search for success rate on their FAQ,
it says we do not publish the success rate
in order to not mislead our customers.
From them, we do not publish success rates
in order not mislead our customers.
I actually got it wrong.
There's a grammatical error there.
Yes, it's we do not publish the success rate
in order not mislead our customers.
Remember that.
Okay, I'm going to click on to just any page
on their website related to data recovery.
Let's click rate.
It says 96% success rate in the title tag.
Have you considered suing yourself?
You don't need my website to say anything.
This is a joke.
Here's the funny thing.
What is a success considered by we recover data?
It says if the client didn't specify the exact critical files
that need to be recovered or indicated all everything
are unknown, we will consider the recovery
to be successful if any files on the media are recovered.
So if I tell you, hey, I'd like to pay you $4,000
to recover everything on this drive
and you recover 64 kilobytes of Windows.DLL files
by this terms of service, that's success.
I never, amazing success rate if my standard was that.
Next day to go over here are the business listing locations.
When you search for data recovery,
you'll see that we recover data shows up first over here.
They show up number one at this Congress Avenue location.
And as you scroll down, again, you'll see
there's a bunch of locations that do not have data recovery
stuff on site.
And my location that actually does have data recovery stuff
on site shows up somewhere in the bottom, if at all.
You got to scroll quite a bit to find that.
Yeah, I don't think you're going to find me at all over here.
Let's take a look at what I said.
Are we recovered data's 50 plus locations, real offices?
We recover data's homepage,
advertises 50 plus global locations.
The 22 addresses investigated are operated virtual offices
by Regis, we work, intelligent office,
and similar co-working providers.
The receptionist reference in the quote
is a Regis for Virtual Office employee,
not re-recover data staff.
The instruction to call us at 866-40032A2
routes to a central call center.
Despite advertising local area codes for cities
like Philadelphia, Houston, the toll free number
is the operational backbone.
The local numbers route to the central call center.
And again, this comes back to what I talked about before.
If you are going to a hardware store,
if you search for hardware store,
you expect that the place that shows up on Google Maps
is going to be a local hardware store
where you can buy screwdrivers and screws and nails.
At the very least, you expected the person
that you see there actually works there.
That's one of the most basic expectations
of having a business.
Now, when you walk into my business, you will see this.
Hello, what is all this?
Hello.
How busy are you?
Yeah, this is a little work.
Point.
We're getting more and more data recoverers,
so I'm happy.
Helian.
Oh, yeah.
She's healing.
This is high grade Helian.
I'm not like this stuff.
They put me balloons at McDonald's.
That's true.
So you use this to put the Helian back in the drive
when you're done?
Yeah.
That's crazy.
You want that?
No.
But I don't want to high grade my pressure Helian.
I fight.
What?
Yeah.
It does work.
Right.
Until you train somebody else and how
to do all the things you know how to do.
There.
Let's walk into their Congress Avenue location
during business hours and see what we get.
OK, so somewhere here, I think, you should find the kind
of items we recover data.
Look like a little one was a bar go.
I'm going to go.
It's here?
OK, let's go.
Let's check.
Let's ask.
There's wait.
There's no we recover data.
And the list.
But it should be.
Let's check.
Excuse me guys, quick question.
I'm looking for we recover data.
It should be somewhere here.
Room 500.
Ask the security.
OK.
Thank you.
Hi, sir.
For a company we recover data, they
should be at room 500.
OK.
They should be open.
The elevator should be open to you.
So you take these seven elevators.
You should be able to go to 500.
Oh, OK.
You see.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, it's a space.
So take that this side over here.
And you should be able to level five.
OK.
500.
Wait.
It's a space.
Hi.
How are you?
Good.
I just have a quick question.
But I'm looking for a we recover data company.
Yes.
So they are they have an office here.
But they are appointment only.
However, from how the device.
You can drop them off here.
Oh, OK.
So actually, I don't have a device with me.
I just have a few questions because honestly,
we lost the pictures from the vacation.
And I don't know the prices.
I don't know anything.
I just have to try to contact them.
Because we don't have that information.
We're kind of like a third party.
So you would have to contact them.
And they'd be able to verify if whatever it is indeed,
if they actually be able to accomplish.
Oh, OK.
So there is no technician.
I thought there was going to be like, we're going to come back.
Thank you, bye.
To be fair to them, almost every data recovery company
does this.
And again, that's why this industry bothers me so much.
That's why I have that honest data recovery
locations on my website.
There are some locations that are not
staffed by recovery data.
This is another company altogether.
At one point, literally had a UPS store mailbox listed
as a data recovery location on Google Maps.
Imagine that you think you're showing up
to a data recovery company that has a lab on site,
and you show up in it's a fucking UPS store.
This is something that happens regularly.
Hiking Mike on the local search forum.com forum found this.
Here's what he had to say about it.
The businesses in this industry have very few real locations.
Just one or single digits, but provide service
to people all over.
So it's not much so spam to have these listings
as it is a tremendous competitive advantage.
It makes them appear far more often and prominently
in search and maps with potentially many listings
in every metro area.
If I looked and counted, I would probably
find they have hundreds of false listings like these.
He actually points to the rules, which I looked up.
And again, I had never reported this company
or any of these other companies to Google.
I'm way too busy and I'm listening.
I'm not that petty.
I'm not going to report you to Google
because you are breaking the rules
of their business listings.
Here's what Google's own rules suggest about this.
Address, Google Business Profile Help.
Businesses can't list an office at a co-working space
unless that office maintains clear signage,
receives customers at the location during business hours,
and is staffed during business hours
by your business staff, not people
from the co-working facility from your business.
Service area businesses or businesses
that serve customers at their locations
should have one profile for the central office
or location with a designated service area.
Service area businesses can't list a virtual office
unless that office is staffed during business hours.
And they even use an example of repair businesses.
Was the receptionist at Chris talking to an employee
if we recover data?
I'm not trying to be petty here.
My employee showed up at their location
because they sent me a threat of litigation.
They think about this in your heart of hearts.
If, let's say that you lost all your stuff
and you realized that you thought you had it backed up
and you didn't, you're panicking, you're losing your mind,
would you rather meet with a we work receptionist or Chris?
I think this is obvious.
I'm just gonna give you my opinion.
In my opinion, the reason that a company would put up
a bunch of addresses where they say that we recover data
when you show up there and there's nobody to recover data
is because it gets you a larger presence.
You can show up in other areas
where you would and otherwise show up
and maybe you get more business.
And by the time the customer who's panicking
and freaked out shows up,
they've already invested in the idea of using you
and it's gonna be inconvenient to research somebody else
so they just say, oh, I guess there's nobody here
that I can talk to, but fine, I'll leave it.
And in my opinion, that's a shitty thing to do to people.
That's deceptive and that's manipulative
at the worst time in somebody's life.
I don't do that.
And yes, I will point out that that is a competitive advantage
that when you show up to my business,
there are actually people there doing data recovery.
That my business does not break Google Maps's guidelines.
If you take a look on the local search forum,
you'll see that for that guy hiking Mike
that was going over salvaged data,
he actually posted on Google support page
trying to get help to remove it.
In early September, I tried to attempt it at its
in Google Maps while I was out there
to market does not existing.
He's referring to this data recovery listing
that's actually a UPS store with a box.
And unless you have some sort of honey,
I shrunk the kid shit with a miniature guy
and penny CC3000 in there,
I'm pretty sure that not to end data recovery
inside of a UPS store box.
At the end of it, a month and a half later
with no progress, he finally asked,
can you ask if this company is white list that are similar?
I've learned this is the thing,
Google somehow proves their setup
and then their listings are considered all in compliance
as by Google's guidelines and they won't move them.
And the guy says, Google won't tell me if they are.
Very helpful.
The exact level of help that you would expect
from a search engine in a company
that lies about me being sponsored by ground news
more than two weeks after I've never had a sponsor.
They don't even have a citation for it.
They just straight up lie.
I've never done a video talking about this
or complaining about this before.
I just kind of sit and take it.
But if you're going to say that I'm not allowed
to talk about this on my own website, all hell no.
Now they complained about me posting stuff
from what people have said on Reddit.
So let's take a look.
What did I do here?
I said, we recovered data.
Publishers no dollar amounts for any service in their website,
which I find to be true.
And I'm comparing contrasting that to the fact
that our website, one of our advantages
is a business in my opinion,
is that we publish quoted price tiers
for every single service that we offer on our website
so that you know exactly what you're getting yourself into.
I can't tell you exactly what's wrong
through drive until I see it.
But what I can say is here are all of our price tiers
so that they cannot change on you later.
When it comes to pricing, I have a part of my website
that has screenshots and links to Reddit threads
where people are talking about prices.
If you're saying that this is illegal,
this is all information that shows up in a Google search.
None of this is magically fabricated.
This is literally screenshots and links
to people who have made Reddit posts about the pricing.
This is a complaint made about me talking about a Zorb 750
as somebody who's on a data recovery forum.
I have a screenshot.
Verify data recovery professionals on Reddit's
R-SLH data recovery have uniformly classified.
We recover data as a marketing driven operation.
They group it alongside pits and secure data recovery
as companies that project nationwide presence
through virtual offices while operating
from centralized facilities.
And I have a link to a post that is made by Zorb 750.
This is literally a screenshot.
I did not say this thing.
I am screenshotting what other people have said.
So if you're saying that me taking a screenshot
and posting what somebody else has said on my site
and attributing that statement to the other person
is illegal.
The exact same thing that shows up on page one of Google
when I searched for the company to begin with.
Prices, I have over here.
It says consumer reported price tiers.
We're I'm saying that consumers, and I'm attributing
the posts to the specific user on Reddit that made it,
have said that these are their full quotes
and I provide you the source on the Reddit forum.
I'm not saying that these are my price quotes that I received.
I'm saying that here's what other people have said on Reddit
about this particular business.
These are screenshots from Reddit
that are attributed to specific users.
I can't use your website as an accurate citation
of what your prices are because you don't list your prices
on your website.
But if any of these price ranges are wrong,
you're more than welcome to correct them
and put a pricing page on your website
that I can reference to say what your prices are in the future.
You would never problem with putting a quoted price
is range on your website, would you?
I know what the answer to that is.
For pricing, I do say that they publish no dollar amounts
for any service in their website.
And you are correct that our site does publish pricing tiers
for the services that we offer.
Everything that we offer, we have a pricing tier four
so that you understand what the price ranges are
before you send us something.
This allows you to make an informed decision.
You know if you have an issue with heads, it's this.
If you have platter damages, that.
If it's a controller issue, it's this.
If it's firmware, it's that.
All of my prices are on my website and clearly stated.
Their demand letter is acting like me using print screen
and taking pictures of what other people have said
on other websites where people discuss customer service
experiences with companies are things
that I have actually said myself.
There is an entire legal framework
for defending against that stuff.
I have over 50 pages of legal defense
already written out and I'm not going to give away
every single part of that in a YouTube video.
At this point, I'm going to read you my response.
Dear Mr. Weston Hauffer.
Rossmann repair grouping and I Rossmann repair group
have received your June 19th letter on behalf
of we recover data.
Rossmann repair denies that the web page
is we recover data safe as false to Famitory
or otherwise harmful and declines the demands
in your letter.
The page will remain published.
The reason is short.
The page consists of a true statements of facts
which are protected, b, statements of opinion based
on facts disclosed to the reader,
which are also protected, and c, accurately attributed
republication of third party statements identified
on the pages such.
Each category is independently protected.
The subjects of the page, the safety, pricing
and advertising of a national data recovery vendor
is a matter of public concern.
Because your letter does not identify
a single specific statement of fact
that is both false and to Famitory,
it lists seven possible causes of action
and broad categories of grievance.
But it does not quote one sentence from the page
and explain how and why that sentence is false.
That is the threshold that we recover data must meet
because on a matter of public concern,
the burden of proving false that he rests
with we recover data, not with Rossmann repair group.
If we recover data, it contends
that a single specific statement is false.
For example, a specific statement about one of its locations,
identify the location and the exact statement
and state the basis for the claim of falsity.
Rossmann repair group will consider any such specific item
on its merits.
The most serious accusations your letter raises
were written by third parties
and are attributed to them on the page.
Rossmann repair group is not the author,
absent a specific false statement,
there is nothing to retract.
The realistic form for these claims is Texas
where Rossmann repair group is located.
Texas is one of the strongest anti-slap statutes in the country,
the Texas Citizens Partispatients Act,
which stays discovery once a motion to dismiss his file
then requires the court to award attorneys fees
to a defendant who prevails in the motion.
A filing and federal court would not avoid
fee and sanctioned exposure.
A groundless claim is subject to rule 11.
And the Lanamaq allows a fee award against a party
that brings an exceptional case.
New York, where your office is located
is not available for them either.
As long as I'm statute,
does not reach an out-of-state speaker
on a defamation claim.
And its own anti-slap statute would shift fees against a plaintiff
who sued over speech in a matter of public interest.
We note these points only to the cause
of an unsuccessful filing as clear the onset.
Your letter asks Rossmann repair to preserve records
and Rossmann repair will meet his preservation obligations.
Tides of the same dispute,
RRG asks that we recover data likewise,
preserve and not delete or alter the records
relevant to these claims,
including the lease or service agreements
for the locations WRD advertises.
The substantiation for its advertised success rate
is terms of service and pricing records,
its records concerning the solicitation
and management of its online reviews.
This request is tied to the dispute your letter describes.
It is not a threat to publicize, report,
or expose anything, and RRG makes no such threat.
I've been on the receiving end of letters like yours before.
From companies a good deal larger than we recover data.
And I want to set out a few points before closing,
because they bear in what we recover data
can realistically expect.
I have published critical factual commentary
about large companies for the most of two decades.
And the man's that I take my commentary down
are not new to me.
In July of 2016, Apple's intellectual property lawyers
contacted me about the repair content on my channel.
The content stayed up.
In 2024, Google sent a cease and desist
to Madden at Greyjay, an independent app
that I've publicly championed stop being offered
within seven days.
We behind the decline, explaining that Greyjay uses no YouTube
API and agreed to none of YouTube's terms,
and it remains available.
In 2025, 2026.
My apologies, typo.
When Bamboo Lab threatened an independent software developer
over an open source tool, I committed $10,000 of our own money
to that developer's defense and hosted the code myself
so that any claim would be brought against me
rather than a party with fewer resources to defend it.
Other companies have sent similar demands over the years.
None of them has let me to take down something I know to be true.
I mentioned this so that my position is not mistaken
for posturing.
I would rather spend money defending a true statement
than pay anything to retract one.
This is a matter of principle, not stubbornness.
Retracting something true would be a misstatement
in its own right.
And it would be a signal that firmly worded letter is
enough to decide what the public has permitted to read.
I am not willing to send that signal,
and I am not deterred by the prospect of a lawsuit.
A letter like Eurosyxedes in most cases
because the recipient would rather take the material down
and bear the cost and disruption of a dispute.
I understand that, and this is where I differ from most people.
I have made a different choice each time,
and I will make the same choice here.
Not only am I not intimidated by litigation,
I sometimes rather miss it.
There are two ways and only two to change what appears
in that page.
Number one, we recovered data can identify specific sentence
and show me that it is false, in which case,
well, correct it promptly and in good faith.
Or we recovered data can obtain a final judgment
to that effect from a court of competent jurisdiction.
Absent one of those things, the page will remain
as published.
I would also be candid about what a lawsuit would accomplish.
Even a complete victory for we recovered data
would not change the fact that the page is accurate,
and the statement's most likely to concern we recovered data
were written by its own customers
and it tributes them on the page.
The suit would also be very costly to WRD.
In Texas, where I am, the anti-slap statute
stays, I'll discover it once a motion to dismiss its file
and requires the court to award a prevailing defendant
as attorney fees.
Discovery would, in the ordinary course,
place WRD's leases, the substantiation
for its advertised success rate, its terms of service,
its review practices into the court record.
I say this not as a threat, and I make no threat
to publicize anything.
I say it because these are the predictable consequences
of filing, and WRD is better served,
weighing them now than after files.
I have no wish to litigate with WRD,
but if WRD chooses that course over identifying
a false statement and allowing me to correct it,
it should expect the page to be defended on its own merits
from start to finish.
RRG would prefer to resolve this without litigation
that benefits no one.
If WRD identifies as a specific statement
it can show as false, RRG will address it.
Otherwise, the page will remain as published,
please direct any further communication
to Rossmann-Apera Groupinc.
Sincerely, Lewis Rossmann, Rossmann-Apera Groupinc.
This is a very, very small sample
of the parts that I found to be the funniest.
You couldn't just call these co-working places
and say like, I'll give you an extra $100 this month
if you could just tell people that we're actually
a data recovery company and that you work for us.
There's something, some preparation, go to your website
and remove the fucking part that has the success rate.
I literally linked to it on my own page
to make it easy for you, to delete the lies.
You didn't even do any cleanup.
I can't, this is with the stuff that I told you.
Way too we go over all the stuff that I haven't told you
because I have 50 pages for this case
that I've been prepared in legal defense
that I haven't shared in this video.
I can't wait to go to court with you.
I can't wait for you to sue me
because something tells me that with the way
that I have done business for almost 20 years
and the way that you have done business,
I have a feeling that discovery is gonna be
a little bit more of an enjoyable process for me
than it is for you.
Here's how this is gonna go.
Number one, I am gonna win on the merits.
Number two, after I win on the merits,
I am going to forget back all of my legal fees,
whether it is $500 or $500,000
because I'm gonna spend a lot of money
to defend what I wrote on my website.
I will get all that money back on Nancy's Slapsuit.
Number three, maybe I'll visit all those locations
that you have around the country.
Maybe I'll go to every single one of them.
I will go there with my camera.
I will record them to see how many of those locations
do or don't have a laminar flow bench or a PC 3000
or a technician that even knows what data recovery is.
And I'll upload those to the Google listings
that you have for your company
that are breaking the Google Maps guidelines.
If they're still there,
if they haven't all been reported by then,
maybe I'll do a tour of the entire country.
Visit every single we recovered data location
and upload video footage of each one
to your Google Maps listing of the reception is saying,
I'm not affiliated, I don't do data recovery,
I don't even work here.
See, I understand why people like you
send the letters that they do.
I've met a lot of people like you.
You think that you're going to intimidate people
into going, no, I'm sorry sir.
Please, I don't think that all the truthful things
I can about you so you can keep doing businesses,
you're wrong.
Please don't say me an angry letter from Zachary.
That is not how I or how Blackberry operates.
In some understand, to any of you out there
that want to send these frivolous cease and desist,
whether it's Google, Apple, Cami research or anybody else
to try and intimidate me by saying,
we're going to enter a legal battle.
I'm not just some random YouTuber
that folds over when I get a legal letter from a lawyer.
I'm a businessman.
I've been a businessman for almost 20 years.
And in these legal battles, in these disputes,
I have never lost, not once.
I'm not locked in here with you.
You're locked in here with me.
And I've only shown you 5% of what I would present to a jury.
And I don't care if it costs me half a million
or a million dollars to do so,
because then I'm going to get it all back.
If that's what you want, send the next letter.
If I don't hear back from you,
I'll consider the disputes settled.
That's it for today.
And as always, I hope you learned something.
I'll see you in the next video.
Bye now.